<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Independence Project</string>

    <!--title fragment-->
    <string name="title_text">Welcome to the Independence Project</string>
    <string name="get_started_button_text">Get Started</string>
    <string name="choose_options_title">Greetings!</string>
    <!--change greeting based on time of day-->

    <string name="breathing_button_text">Breathing Exercise</string>
    <string name="quotes_button_text">Handling emotions</string>
    <string name="madlib_button_text">Default String</string>

    <!--Breathing Texts-->
    <string name="inhale_text">Inhale</string>
    <string name="exhale_text">Exhale</string>
    <string name="breathing_popup_text1">The following animation was designed to help you relax.</string>
    <string name="breathing_popup_text2">Inhale with your nose and exhale with your mouth.</string>
    <string name="timer_count">0</string>

    <!--Empathy Game Texts-->
    <string name="quotes_page_instructions">Pick out an emotion</string>
    <string name="quotes_page_instructions2">We will provide you with tips and quotes to help you through your day. You are never alone.</string>
    <string name="got_it_popup">Got It</string>

    <!--emotions-->
    <string name="happy_face_text">Happy</string>
    <string name="scared_face_text">Scared</string>
    <string name="angry_face_text">Angry</string>
    <string name="nervous_face_text">Nervous</string>
    <string name="sad_face_text">Sad</string>

    <string name="game_question">Pick out an emotion</string>
    <string name="get_quote_button">Generate Quote</string>

    <!--happy quote list-->
    <string-array name="happy_quote_list">
        <item>The secret to happiness is freedom. And the secret to freedom is courage</item>
        <item>Action may not always Bring happiness, But there is no happiness without action.</item>
        <item>Every man is happy until happiness is suddenly a goal.</item>
        <item>We don\'t develop courage By Being happy every day. We develop it By surviving difficult times and challenging adversity.</item>
        <item>The most important thing is to enjoy your life - to Be happy - it\'s all that matters.</item>
        <item>Being happy never goes out of style.</item>
        <item>Sometimes your joy is the source of your smile, But sometimes your smile can Be the source of your joy.</item>
        <item>Happy people plan actions, they don\’t plan results.</item>
        <item>Very little is needed to make a happy life; it is all within yourself, in your way of thinking.</item>
        <item>The foolish man seeks happiness in the distance, the wise grows it under his feet.</item>
        <item>No act of kindness, no matter how small, is ever wasted.</item>
        <item>No one can make you feel inferior without your consent.</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--scared quote list-->
    <string-array name="scared_quote_list">
        <item>The scariest thing is setting your goals too low and meeting them.
        -Georges Saint Pierre</item>
        <item>Many a false step was made By standing still.</item>
        <item>Feel fear and do it anyway.</item>
        <item>Courage is Being scared to death... and saddling up anyway.</item>
        <item>Only those who will risk going too far can possiBly find out how far one can go.</item>
        <item>Don\'t fear failure so much that you refuse to try new things. The saddest summary of a life contains three descriptions: could have, might have, and should have.</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--angry quote list-->
    <string-array name="angry_quote_list">
        <item>For every minute you remain angry, you give up sixty seconds of peace of mind.
        -Ralph Waldo Emerson</item>
        <item>When angry count to ten Before you speak. If very angry, count to one hundred.
            -Thomas Jefferson</item>
        <item>I am a danger to myself if I get angry.
            -Oriana Fallaci</item>
        <item>When anger rises, think of the consequences.
        -Confucius</item>
        <item>It\’s okay to Be angry, it\’s never okay to Be cruel.</item>
        <item>When angry count to ten Before you speak. If very angry, count to one hundred.</item>
        <item>The strongest people are not those who show strength in front of us, But those who win Battles we know nothing aBout.</item>
        <item>Everytime you are aBle to find some humor in a difficult situation, you win.</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--nervous quote list-->
    <string-array name="nervous_quote_list">
        <item>Nothing fails like success</item>
        <item>If you can dream it, you can do it.
        -Walt Disney</item>
        <item>Being nervous isn\'t Bad, it just means something important is happening.
        -Anonymous</item>
        <item>If you don\'t try, there’s no opportunity to succeed.
        -Katie Lime</item>
        <item>Life Begins at the end of your comfort zone.
        -Anonymous</item>
        <item>Don\'t let your mind Bully your Body into Believing it must carry the Burden of its worries.
        -Astrid Alauda</item>
        <item>Every time you are tempted to react in the same old way, ask if you want to Be a prisoner of the past or a pioneer of the future.
        -Deepak Chopra</item>
        <item>Smile, Breathe, and go slowly.
        -Thich Nhat Hanh</item>

    </string-array>

    <!--sad quote list-->
    <string-array name="sad_quote_list">
        <item>The purpose of life is to Be defeated By greater and greater things.</item>
        <item>"Don't cry Because it\'s over, smile Because it happened."
        ― Dr. Seuss</item>
        <item>"You cannot protect yourself from sadness without protecting yourself from happiness."
        ― Jonathan Safran Foer</item>
        <item>"Tears shed for another person are not a sign of weakness. They are a sign of a pure heart."
        ― José N. Harris, MI VIDA: A Story of Faith, Hope and Love</item>
        <item>"Be strong, Because things will get Better. It may Be stormy now, But it never rains forever. </item>
        <item>"Nothing can cure the soul But the senses, just as nothing can cure the senses But the soul."
        ― Oscar Wilde, The Picture of Dorian Gray</item>
        <item>Curiosity will conquer fear even more than Bravery will.
           -James Stephens</item>
        <item>"Sad? Depressed? HeartBroken? Feeling like world\'s going to end tomorrow?
        No worries, there’s a Taylor Swift song for that"</item>
        <item>"Whenever you feel sad, just rememBer that there\'s someone in the world who is pulling a door that says push."</item>
        <item>"Take a step and Breathe. It\'s a Bad day, not a Bad life."</item>
        <item>"Ice cream does wonders for a heavy heart. Frozen yogurt is proBaBly healthier though." </item>
        <item>Here\'s a joke:
        They all laughed when I said I wanted to Be a comedian. Well, they\'re not laughing now</item>
        <item>Everytime I\'m sad, I imagine a T-Rex trying to put a hat on. </item>
        <item>"Exercise is good for your Body and mind. Nudge nudge, wink wink."</item>
        <item>May the Force Be with you.
            And the Happiness.
            And the Love.</item>
        <item>Every human walks around with a certain kind of sadness. They may not wear it on their sleeves, But it\'s there if you look deep.
        -Taraji P. Henson</item>
        <item>Fear is only as deep as the mind allows.
        -Japanese ProverB</item>
        <item>Take BaBy steps, Rome wasn\'t Built in a day.</item>
        <item>Make sure you get enough sleep. If you can\'t, coffee helps too.</item>
        <item>Pain is inevitaBle, But suffering is optional.</item>
        <item> Healing doesn\'t mean you were never hurt, it means you no longer allow the hurt to control you. </item>
        <item> When everything goes wrong and things seem to fall apart?
        When noBody Believes in you and you feel so alone?
        This is the EXACT moment that you got to Believe in yourself. </item>
        <item>If you can\'t fly, then run, if you can\'t run, then walk, if you can\'’t walk, then crawl, But whatever you do, you have to keep moving forward.</item>
        <item>The ones who are crazy enough to think they can change the world are the ones that do.</item>
    </string-array>



</resources>

